Contact

katrina.brown57@gmail.com

www.linkedin.com/in/katrina-brownmsn-rn-cnor-6bb89846 (LinkedIn) FortisCollege.edu (Company) gmail.com (Personal)

Top Skills

Organizational Development Health Education Surgery Nurse

Katrina Brown, MSN, RN, CNOR

Operating Room Travel Nurse

Savannah, Georgia Area

Summary

Experienced Nursing with a demonstrated history of working in the hospital & health care industry. Skilled in Clinical Research, Nursing Education, Patient Education, Organizational Development, and Cardiopulmonary Resuscitation (CPR). Strong information technology professional with a Master of Science focused in Nursing Administration from The Ohio State University.

Experience

Cross Country TravCorps
Operating Room Travel Nurse
September 2017 - Present (2 years 10 months)

OhioHealth
Nursing Administrator
November 2007 - Present (12 years 8 months)
Doctors Hospital, 5100 West Broad Street, Columbus, Ohio 43228

Dublin Methodist Hospital Surgery Coordinator October 2015 - September 2017 (2 years) Dublin, Ohio

Fortis College-Columbus
Nursing Skills/Simulation Lab Coordinator
April 2015 - October 2015 (7 months)

Education Affiliates
Nursing Faculty
February 2009 - April 2015 (6 years 3 months)
Fortis College-Columbus, Ohio

Doctors Hospital, OhioHealth Staff Nurse, Surgery November 2007 - April 2015 (7 years 6 months) 5100 west broad street, columbus, ohio 43228

CNOR (Certified Operating Room Nurse). I have demonstrated the knowledge and skill that shows competency in the area of Perioperative nursing. My certification is committed to providing quality patient care to all my surgical patients.

Education

The Ohio State University

Master of Science, Nursing Administration · (2003 - 2008)